um how much HTML do you need to
learn how much do you really need um
I've talked about this before but I want
to say it again everybody in the tech
World expects you to know enough HTML to
be able to create documentation uh
there's another video that goes very
deeply into the different types of web
that exist the primary method the
primary web being the document web um
that's it that's it you don't need to
know more than that and very
specifically that means you only need to
learn as much HTML and CSS and XML I
guess um to correspond with the same
things that you should have at this
point already learned in
markdown um you know italics uh
bold um you know how to make a paragraph
how to embed in image um these are
pretty basic HTML things and one of the
great things about having that be the
the beginning of your knowledge with
regard to web development is because you
can actually use a markdown renderer and
you can see what the renderer does how
it produces HTML and you can go back and
forth between the two and and alter them
and strictly speaking as we talked about
in the other markdown video markdown
itself the original markdown specifies
that HTML should be able to be used
inside of a markdown document I strongly
suggest against that but but strictly
speaking the original uh markdown
included HTML that means learning how to
write inline
HTML um was a part of the workflow of
the people who invented markdown and as
you know that included writers and
Publishers not so much scientists so so
HTML is designed to be really easy to
write uh for for that purpose um you do
not need to know all of the the Deep
things that you're going to need to know
about that and separate video uh I'm
going to go over all of the different
places where you can go look up uh
information about HTML and try to figure
out how to make web pages beyond that so
if you want to take your knowledge some
place further than that uh there's
another video that goes through all the
places that you can go find that stuff
out so so so all you need to do is learn
enough HTML to cover markdown